[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Now when you saw the car, what did it tell you about what may have happened here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "It told me something was really wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "Do you think he has it in him to keep safe in an environment, in the one that he's in now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Well, Piers, he's a tough kid, he's in great shape, and he's really smart, but I'm afraid that he's not geared up for this environment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "What would you like to say to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "I would say, hey, we all make mistakes and it doesn't matter how far out you are, or what's happened, we want you to come home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Croom"]}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "When you hear a story like the one I've just described about Jonathan Croom, and you see the anguish of his farther, it must bring back very vivid memories for both of you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Yes, those memories never die, of course, and we wanted to just talk to Mr. Croom.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jonathan Croom"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "And what do you say to youngsters who want to follow him -- in Christopher's footsteps like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": ".", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christopher"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Realistically, how easy is it to survive in that situation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Well, you know, it really depends on what you start with in terms of your physical health and what resources you have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Do you believe there is a link?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Well, I think common sense would have you think, certainly in the case of this 8-year-old boy, that there is some sort of association here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "What do you think of that phenomenon amongst young people these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Yes, I mean, and I've seen this before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "What do you make of it, now that you've had a bit of time to really assess it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Well, I still think it goes back to his childhood trauma.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "Is there enough being done either at the state level or federal level to tackle what many think is the root cause behind so much of the violence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "JJ", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "I completely agree.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Darfur"]}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "So, George Tunis, tell me why you came up with this or why you think it would work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Our company is an armor company, full of engineers, and throughout the war and several Darfur contracts we were able to create armor that protected our troops overseas.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Tunis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NIJ"]}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PDT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ":", "NNS", "IN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "CD", ",", "RB", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Can it stop an AR-15 in the hands of somebody like Adam Lanza?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "We make all levels of armor, so the armor that we've outfitted many school with -- schools with is NIJ Level 3A, so that's exactly the same armor that would be in a police vest.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam Lanza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Are you supportive of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "I mean, my argument would be, how does this stop somebody like Adam Lanza with an AR-15 and a hundred bullet magazine, for example?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "It's a great question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam Lanza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "But you're doing more for genuinely bulletproof doors?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "And this is the kind of thing you're talking about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Well, this is -- not -- you know, this is shop (ph) -- we make corporate room ballistic doors out of this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "ORGAN: Are they -- are they prohibitively (ph) expensive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", ":", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "So schools around America could have these relatively cheaply?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "I think so, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Are you a parent yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I have two kids in school.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "How do you feel about my just concern about the militarizing of -- of educational process to kids?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "You know, I think kids should be able to go to school in a -- in an environment that is not full of fear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "And would that door, would that substance stop an AR-15?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "No, this -- this door would not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "He's supportive of a military strike against Syria and its regime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "I think at this point, when America says there's a thin red line in the international community, most civilized nations agree with that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "I didn't say they got the story wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "What is your response to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "You know, I actually was hoping to see this movie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ashton Kutcher"]}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "Steve jobs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "Ashton Kutcher's impression of Jobs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Get your (inaudible) feet (ph) out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "What are you going to do, you're going to fire me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "No, I already fired you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Is that like Steve Jobs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "There were a lot of incidences of Steve Jobs' history that were like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "DT", ",", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Are you hoping the Aaron Sorkin (ph) version, the -- the movie that he is bringing out about Steve Jobs will be a little bit more realistic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "NN", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "I was hoping this movie would be, a, realistic or if not realistic, it's very excited and entertaining.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Aaron Sorkin", "Steve Jobs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "You haven't flown since 9/11, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "I'm the wrong person to ask.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "How many hours of sleep do you need in life, Steve?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "It depends.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Does that actually happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "It happened a lot in the old days.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Well, what do and Kanye talk about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "You know, we had some nice discussions about some of his ideas for a business he sees.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Wozniak"]}, "docId": "130826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "You've got $2 bills?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "$", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "Yes, Steve Wozniak, one of my favorite guests.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$2 bills"]}}]